web2list.com 2009-06-16

# Web 2.0, Web 2.0 News, Web 2.0 Sites, Web 2.0 Lists

We here at Web2List.com recognize that your privacy is very important. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy guidelines. Since this is a growing website and because Internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change and any changes will be posted on this page. Any material changes from current practices will be posted on the main page of this website to serve as notice.

Web2List.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which it may link.

### Personal Information

During registration for membership, we may collect personal information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for more information.

We usually collect personal information directly from you although sometimes we may use agents or service providers to do this for us.

When you are online, we collect information regarding the pages within our network that you visit.

We may also acquire lists from other sources, both from other companies and from other public documents.

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We collect no information on consumers who browse our website.

### Use of Information

We use your information to provide our services to you, to fulfill administrative functions associated with these services, for example billing, to enter into contracts with you or third parties and for marketing and client relationship purposes.

You may receive e-mail from us to let you know about new products, services and upcoming events that may interest you. If you do not want to receive an e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the address provided below.

We may make our customer and user e-mail list and other information available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address and/or other information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by e-mailing us at the address provided below. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

We may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

### Children 

We may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

### Privacy on the Internet

  * Remember to close your browser when you have finished your user session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer.
  * Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information over the Internet that this information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information in publicly accessible online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. ****
  * Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username and passwords and any account information. ****
  * Please be careful and responsible whenever you are using the Internet. ****
